<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Selfly</string>
    <string name="dialogue_title">Are You Sure?</string>
    <string name="dialogue_text">Once you enter this entry you will be able to view it, however, you will not be able to edit it unless you create a new entry. Are you sure you are done?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="calm_done">This will send you back to the home screen, are you sure?</string>
    <string name="delete_all">This will delete all past entries and send you back to home screen. Are you sure you want to delete all past entries?</string>
    <string-array name="mood_array">
        <item>very happy</item>
        <item>happy</item>
        <item>calm</item>
        <item>sad</item>
        <item>very sad</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="tip1">1. Keep physically active\n
            Develop a routine so that you\'re physically active most days of the week. Exercise is a powerful stress reducer.
            It can improve your mood and help you stay healthy.</string>
    Start out slowly, and gradually increase the amount and intensity of your activities.
    <string name="tip2">2. Avoid alcohol and recreational drugs.\n
            These substances can cause or worsen anxiety. If you can\'t
            quit on your own, see your health care provider or find a support group to help you.</string>
    <string name="tip3">3. Quit smoking, and cut back or quit drinking caffeinated beverages.\n
        Nicotine and caffeine can worsen anxiety.</string>
    <string name="tip4">4. Use stress management and relaxation techniques.\n
        Visualization techniques, meditation and yoga are examples of relaxation techniques that can ease anxiety.</string>
    <string name="tip5">5. Make sleep a priority.\n
        Do what you can to make sure you\'re getting enough sleep to feel rested. If you aren\'t sleeping well, talk with your health care provider.</string>
    <string name="tip6">6. Eat healthy foods.\n
        A healthy diet that incorporates vegetables, fruits, whole grains and fish may be linked to reduced anxiety, but more research is needed.</string>
    <string name="tip7">7. Learn about your disorder.\n
        Talk to your health care provider to find out what might be causing your specific condition and what treatments might be best for you. Involve your family and
            friends, and ask for their support.</string>
    <string name="tip8">8. Stick to your treatment plan.\n
Take medications as directed. Keep therapy appointments and complete any assignments your therapist gives. Consistency can make a big difference, especially when it comes to
            taking your medication.</string>
    <string name="tip9">9. Identify triggers.\n
Learn what situations or actions cause you stress or increase your anxiety. Practice the strategies you developed with your mental health provider so you\'re ready to
            deal with anxious feelings in these situations.</string>
    <string name="tip10">10. Keep a journal.\n
Keeping track of your personal life can help you and your mental health provider identify what\'s causing you stress and what seems to help you feel better.</string>
    <string name="tip11">11. Socialize.\n
Don\'t let worries isolate you from loved ones or activities.</string>
    <string name="care1">1. Physical Self-Care\n
The mind and body connection is a real phenomenon. When you are caring for your body, you\’ll think and feel better too.
        Physical self-care includes how you\'re fueling your body, how much sleep
        you\'re getting, how much physical activity you are doing, and how well you\'re caring for your physical needs.
        Attending appointments, taking medication as prescribed, and managing your health are all part of good physical self-care.
        Here are some questions you can ask yourself to assess your physical health:\n
        Am I getting adequate sleep?\n
        Is my diet fueling my body well?\n
        Am I taking charge of my health?\n
        Am I getting enough exercise?</string>
    <string name="care2">2. Social Self-Care\n
        We are not meant to live in total isolation - we all need social connectivity to thrive in life. Although it can be hard to make time for
        family and friends with our busy schedules, close connections are important for our well-being. Here are some fun ideas to try. If these activities
        below don’t resonate with you, try something that would.\n
        Watch a fun movie with friends\n
        Call a parent\n
        Have dinner with your special someone\n
        Family game night\n
        Volunteer for a cause that is important to you</string>
    <string name="care3">3. Mental Self-Care\n
       Did you know that humans have about 6200 thoughts in a single day? Don\’t you think our self-talk will affect how we think and feel about ourselves?
        It\’s also important to stimulate your mind with mental activities. Here are some mental activities to try:\n
        Practice self-compassion and acceptance\n
        Choose positive thoughts more often\n
        Choose kindness\n
        Do a puzzle\n
        Learn something new</string>
    <string name="care4">4. Spiritual Self-Care\n
        Nurturing your spirit doesn\’t have to involve religion, though for some it does. It can involve anything that helps you develop a deeper sense of meaning,
        understanding or connection with the universe. Here are a few examples.\n
        Meditation\n
        Yoga\n
        Going to a place of worship\n
        Being in nature\n
        Self-reflection</string>
    <string name="care5">5. Emotional Self-Care\n
        It is important to have healthy coping skills to deal with uncomfortable emotions like anger, anxiety, and sadness.
        Emotional self-care is a process in which we bring our awareness to our emotions and take the steps necessary in order to honor and care for
        these emotions. Here are some activities that can be helpful for emotional self-care.\n
        Talk to a friend you can trust\n
        Journal your feelings\n
        Meditation\n
        Gratitude\n
        Take a break</string>
    <string name="love1">
        1. Do Something Kind\n
        Although it might seem like a slightly selfish motive, being kind and doing something for someone less fortunate than yourself can help you learn to love
        yourself.
        There are lots of different ways to do something kind, but one of the best, long-term ways you can do something for someone else is by volunteering.
        If you fancy giving this a go, pick a volunteer opportunity that suits you and your skill set. For example, you could help out at a local swimming club,
        befriend an elderly person or use your marketing experience to promote a local charity.
    </string>
    <string name="love2">2. Become Your Hero For The Day\n
        If you have something important coming up that you don\’t feel confident about, such as an interview or a speech you have to deliver, you might find
        that pretending
        to be your hero for the day can give you that hit of confidence you need to pull it off.\n

        If you want to try this out for yourself choose someone that you can identify with, but who is also well known for his or her confidence. Then begin to act
        like them. Although you don\’t have to speak in their accent or use any of their quirky mannerisms, envisioning your hero can have a surprisingly positive
        impact upon your own body language and tone of voice. </string>
    <string name="love3">3. Retrain Your Thoughts\n

A great way to alter your behaviour and learn to love yourself is to retrain the way you think. You can do this by following up every negative
        thought you have about yourself with a positive. For example, if you tell yourself that you are ugly, old or overweight, follow this bad thought up with
        something positive, like: ‘I have great skin, hair and a good smile’. Increasing the number of positive thoughts you have about yourself during the day
        will hopefully help you to enjoy being you and will help to boost your self-esteem.</string>
    <string name="love4">4. Admit Your Flaws And Take Action\n
We all have flaws and that\’s fine. It is just something that we have to accept. Yet some people\’s flaws can interfere with their life and become an obstacle
        that stands between them and their happiness. If you have a flaw that is becoming a problem it is time to admit that you need to change.\n

You might have a foul temper, have an issue with food, be cripplingly jealous or be going through a wild phase that has become out of control.
        Whatever your flaw, remember that you will be unable to love yourself until you address these issues and you will feel a million times better
        about yourself if you seek some help.</string>
    <string name="love5">5. Relationship Analysis\n
There are some people in this life that are just no good for us. If you have friends, boyfriends, girlfriends or colleagues who undermine you,
        belittle you or are just plain mean, you need to have a think about addressing the issue and confronting them about their behaviour.\n

Remember that no one has the right to put you down and the only way people
        will stop acting in this way is if they know you won\’t accept it. Be brave, plan what you are going to say so that you can communicate clearly and
        then sit down and talk through your issue face to face. If the problem continues it might be time to consider cutting them out of your life altogether.\n
</string>
    <string name="sleep1">1. Invest in a Better Mattress and Bedding\n
    2. Block Out Light\n
    3. Minimize Noise\n
    4. Set the Thermostat to 65 to 68 Degrees Fahrenheit\n
    5. Get at Least Seven Hours of Sleep
    </string>
    <string name="sleep2">6. Set Your Alarm for the Same Time Each Day\n
    7. Keep Naps Around 20 Minutes\n
    8. Relax for 30 Minutes Before Bed\n
    9. Disconnect Devices in the Hour Before Bed\n
    10. Get 30 Minutes of Natural Light Exposure
    </string>
    <string name="sleep3">11. Exercise for at Least 20 Minutes Each Day\n
    12. Limit Caffeine After 2 p.m.\n
    13. Be Mindful of Alcohol in the Hour Before Bedtime\n
    14. Eat Dinner a Few Hours Before Bed\n
    15. Limit Nicotine Use and Smoke Exposure
    </string>
    <string name="sleep4">16. Reserve Your Bed for Sleep Only\n
    17. Get Out of Bed After 20 Minutes\n
    18. Keep a Sleep Diary\n
    19. Consider Supplements\n
    20. Talk With a Doctor
    </string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about_the_app">࣪ ִֶָ☾. About The App ࣪ ִֶָ☾.</string>
    <string name="about">As someone who has always struggled with mental health, I wanted to make an app that would be useful to me and others. I love journaling, but find it annoying to have a physical one. I wanted to make a little pretty app, for my little pretty journaling--that was the main idea when making this. I loved making this app, I hope you love it as much as I do!</string>
    <string name="anxiety_tips">★⭑ANXIETY TIPS!⭑★</string>
    <string name="view_website">View Website</string>
    <string name="click_for_next_tip">★⭑Click For Next Tip!⭑★</string>
    <string name="and_remember_you_are_loved">And Remember You Are Loved</string>
    <string name="let_s_slow_it_down">let\'s slow it down...</string>
    <string name="breathe_in">BREATHE IN...</string>
    <string name="i_m_done">i\'m done!</string>
    <string name="new_entry"><![CDATA[new entry ->]]></string>
    <string name="journal">✦ JOURNAL ✦</string>
    <string name="tips_tips_tips">TIPS TIPS TIPS</string>
    <string name="what_do_you_need_a_tip_for">what do you need a tip for?</string>
    <string name="anxiety">anxiety</string>
    <string name="sleep">sleep</string>
    <string name="self_love">self love</string>
    <string name="self_care">self care</string>
    <string name="write_it_out">°。write it out 。°</string>
    <string name="type_here">type here...</string>
    <string name="enter">enter</string>
    <string name="enter_title">Enter Title</string>
</resources>